So it seems like this lnternet thing
is here to stay, huh?
다들 인터넷이라도 하고 있나?
It's okay not to talk.
얘기 안 해도 괜찮아
Hey, you guys, guess what.
얘들아, 있잖아
-Barry and Mindy are getting a divorce.
-Oh, my God.
배리랑 민디가 이혼한대
세상에
What is the matter with you?
너 도대체 왜 그러냐?
No. Barry and Mindy.
아니, 배리랑 민디라고
미안
Oh, sorry. I hear "divorce,"
I immediately go to Ross.
이혼이라니까
로스가 떠오르잖아
Who's Barry and Mindy?
배리랑 민디가 누군데?
배리는 내가 결혼할 뻔한 남자고
민디는 가장 친한 친구였어
Barry was the guy that I almost married,
and Mindy was my best friend.
배리가 너 몰래
민디를 만났지?
Wasn't he cheating on you with her?
그래서 배리는 나 대신
민디 위에서 잠들게 됐지
But that just means he was falling
asleep on top of her instead of me.
-Why did they get divorced?
-Well, apparently...
왜 이혼한대?
배리가 바람피우다
민디한테 걸렸나 봐
she caught him cheating on her
with someone else.
Isn't that sad?
깨소금 맛이지?
만약 배리랑 결혼했으면
내 삶이 어떻게 변했을까?
Can you imagine if I'd married him?
How different would my life be?
그러게
I've always wondered
how different my life would be...
이혼 안 했더라면 내 인생도
얼마나 달라졌을지 궁금해
if I'd never gotten divorced.
- 몇 번째 이혼?
- 첫 번째
-Which time?
-The first time!
캐롤이 자기가 레즈비언이란
사실을 몰랐다고 가정해 봐
Imagine if Carol hadn't realized
she was a lesbian.
상상이 안 돼
좋은 것만 보인다
I can't.
I keep seeing it the good way.
I bet I'd still be doing my karate.
난 아직 카라테를
하고 있을 거야
Towards the end of our marriage,
I did a lot of karate to release the tension...
이혼할 즈음에
카라테 열심히 했었거든
쌓이는 건 많은데
달리 힘쓸 일이 없다보니
from not doing anything
else physical.
카라테를 발음하는 게
문제 아니었을까?
Maybe the problem was
you were pronouncing it "ka-ra-tay."
내가 여전히 뚱뚱하다면?
What if I was still fat?
You wouldn't be dating me,
that's for sure.
자긴 분명히 날
거들 떠도 안 봤겠지
-Sure I would.
-Come on.
무슨 소리야
그래, 어련하시겠다
You guys really think I'm that shallow?
내가 그렇게 얍삽한 애로 보여?
아니, 모니카가 그렇게
두터웠단 얘기야
No, I just think Monica
was that fat.
내가 아직 '생의 나날들'에
출연하고 있었다면?
Hey, imagine if I'd never got fired
off Days of Our Lives.
Hey. Hey, there's Carol again.
야, 또 캐롤 나온다
만약 내가 과감하게
사표를 던졌다면?
What if I had had the guts
to quit my job?
I'd probably be writing for
The New Yorker, being paid to be funny.
아마 '뉴요커'에 조크를
기고하고 있을 거야
But my job's fun too.
I mean, tomorrow...
지금 일도 재미있어
내일은 넥타이 안 매도 되거든
I don't have to wear a tie.
What if I'd taken that job
at Merrill Lynch?
내가 메릴 린치의 스카우트
제의를 받아들였다면?
-What?
-Merrill Lynch?
- 뭐야?
- 메릴 린치?
거기 근무하던 마사지 손님이
내가 주식에 감각이 있댔거든
I had a massage client who worked there,
and he said I had a knack for stocks.
근데 왜 안 들어갔어?
Why didn't you take the job?
당시엔 압운이 맞는 건
모두 진실인 줄 알았어
Because at that time, I thought that
everything that rhymed was true.
I thought if I worked with stocks...
'주식' 일을 하게 되면
'재래식' 주택에 살면서
I'd have to live in a box
and only eat lox and have a pet fox.
'간식'만 먹고
'숙식'도 해결 못하잖아
Yeah, you don't want that
in a broker.
브로커가 그렇게 살면 비참하지
인생이 그렇게 풀렸더라도
우리가 아직 친구일까?
Do you guys think if all those things
happened, we'd still hang out?
The One That Could Have Been
Oh, my God. Rachel Green?
세상에, 레이첼 그린?
Rob Tilman!
롭 틸먼
No, no, it's me. Ross.
아냐, 나야
로스
미안, 로스 틸먼
Oh, I'm sorry. Ross Tilman.
아니지, 로스 겔러
-No. No, no. Ross Geller.
-Of course! Monica's brother.
맞다, 모니카 오빠
그래, 맞았어
-Yeah. Right.
-Wow! How are you?
잘 지내?
그럼, 나 결혼했어
Good. Good. I'm married.
나도
Me too!
- 결혼하니까 좋지?
- 두말하면 잔소리
-Isn't it the best?
-Oh, it's the best.
-So how's Monica?
-Really, really great.
모니카는 어때?
걔도 잘 지내
Actually, she's right down the street.
You should stop by and say hi.
실은 길 건너편에 있는데
잠깐 들러서 인사나 할래?
그거 좋지
-I would love to.
-She'd be so excited.
너무 반가워하겠다
-Okay.
-Come on.
- 그래
- 가자
Wait, don't you have
to pay for...
잠깐, 책값 내야지...
Busty Ladies?
젖소 부인?
No, that's okay. Some kid asked me
to pick it up for him, but I....
아냐, 어떤 꼬마 녀석이
사달라고 부탁하지 뭐야
그랬구나
가자고
그럼 돈은 돌려줘야지
Don't you have to give him
his money back?
야, 이거 다시 받아라
미안하지만 포르노는 안 돼
Here you go, buddy.
Sorry, no porn for you.
그럼 모니카한테 가자
Okay, let's go see Monica.
So, Monica.
Still going out with Dr. Boring, huh?
모니카, 아직도 저 따분한
의사 만나냐?
따분한 게 아니라 그냥...
He's not boring. He's just...
He's low-key.
점잖아서 그래
- 여기 헤이즐넛 라테
- 고마워요
-Here you go, one hazelnut latte.
-Thank you.
You know, the hazelnut,
actually not a nut.
혹시 알아요? 사실 헤이즐넛은
열매라 아니라 씨앗이라는 거
It's a seed.
Wow.
실제로는 씨앗인데 열매로
알려진 게 또 뭔지 알아요?
Can anyone else name a well-known seed
that's been masquerading as a nut?
맙소사, 어디 보자...
Oh, dear God. Let me think.
나 왔다
무슨 일 있어?
What's the matter?
또 퇴짜 맞았다
I got another rejection letter.
They said my writing was funny,
just not "Archie Comic" funny.
내 글이 재미는 있는데
'아치 만화'의 재미는 아니래
I gotta get back to the hospital.
병원에 들어가봐야겠어
- 그래요
- 잘들 있어요
-Bye.
-Bye-bye.
By the way, the answer is:
the Brazil nut.
그건 그렇고 정답은
브라질 호두예요
질문이 '저 친구보다
더 따분한 건?' 이었냐?
Was his question,
"What's more boring than him?"
조끼 한번 가관이다
And nice sweater vest,
by the way.
-Stop it, guys. He's sweet.
-Yeah, yeah.
그만해, 좋은 사람이야
그래, 맞아
Hey, man.
Sorry about the Archie thing.
이번 일은 안됐다
혹시 돈 필요하냐?
You need me to
give you some money?
I may have no money,
but I still have my pride.
내가 돈은 없을지언정
자존심은 남아있어
진짜?
Really?
에...
네가 꼭 돈을 줄 필요는 없어
인기스타는 조수를 두잖아?
Joey doesn't have to give you the money.
-TV stars have assistants, right?
-That's an idea.
좋은 생각이다
내 조수가 주는 돈은 받을래?
If I hire an assistant,
would you take money from her?
그게 아니라 챈들러를
조수로 쓰라는 뜻이야
No, Joey.
Chandler could be your assistant.
네 팬레터에 답장도 써주고
He could answer
all your fan mail and stuff.
그거 좋다, 그렇게 하자
-That would be great! Let's do that!
-I could use the money.
돈도 벌고
글 쓸 시간도 생기겠네
I'd have time to write.
- 그래, 취직 축하한다
- 좋았어
-Great. Welcome aboard!
-Okay!
All right. Now, I need to use the bathroom.
자, 이제...
난 화장실에 갈 건데
거기선 조수 필요 없으니까
Since I don't need any assistance
in there, take a break!
- 푹 쉬어
- 좋지
All right.
- 얘들아
- 어서 와, 피비
-Hey.
-Hey, Phoebe.
Guess what. Joey just hired
Chandler to be his assistant.
- 이거 알아?
- 뭘?
조이가 챈들러를
조수로 채용했어
That's so sweet.
그거 잘됐네
Oh! Hang on!
잠깐
기다려, 임마
Hang on!
뭐야
Go!
아냐, 아니지
50이 되면 팔랬잖아
No. No, no.
I said sell when it hits 50!
Five-oh! It's a number!
It comes after four-nine!
49 다음에 오는 50 몰라?
괜찮아, 그래
실수 한 번쯤이야 뭐
No, it's okay. It's okay.
You're allowed one mistake.
Just kidding.
You are, of course, fired.
농담이네, 넌 해고야
Oh, what a shame.
I really liked her.
진짜 맘에 드는 애였는데
- 야, 모니카
- 어서 와
Hey, Mon?
Mon, look who I ran into!
누가 왔는지 봐라
Oh, my God, Rachel!
맙소사, 레이첼
너 정말 근사하다
-God, you look terrific!
-So do you!
너도 그래
살 좀 뺀 거야?
-Did you lose weight?
-You are so sweet to notice.
알아주니 고맙다
3.5파운드 빠졌어
Yes, I lost 3.5 pounds!
You remember my friend Chandler.
- 내 친구 챈들러 기억나지?
- 접니다
- 안녕하세요
- 저쪽은 피비야
-And that's Phoebe over there.
-Hi.
반가워요
세상에, 어서 앉아봐
Sit down. How long has it
been since we've seen each other?
우리 언제 보고 못 봤지?
1987, the day after Christmas.
Sean McMahan's party.
1987년 크리스마스 다음날
숀 맥메이헌의 파티였는데
I played you one of my songs, you know,
"lnterplanetary Courtship Ritual."
너한테 내 곡을 들려줬어
'행성 간 짝짓기 의식'
Oh, yeah. Right.
그래, 맞다
-So, now, do you still do music?
-Well, sometimes.
아직도 음악 하니?
가끔
-Come over sometime. I'll play you..
-Oh, my God!
- 듣고 싶으면 나중에...
- 어머나
'생의 나날들'의
조이 트리비아니가
Joey Tribbiani from Days of Our Lives
just walked in here!
방금 들어왔어
레이첼, 쟤 우리 친구야
-Rach, he's a friend of ours.
-You're friends with Dr. Drake Ramoray?
너희들이 드레이크
라모레 박사랑 친구야?
드레이크와 친구가 되긴 힘들죠
It's hard to be friends with Drake...
because of his busy schedule
and the fact that he's not real.
바쁘기도 하지만
실존인물이 아니거든요
Hey, or I could bring
my keyboard here sometime.
저기, 그럼 내가 아예
키보드를 이리 가져올게
얘, 이리 온다
-He's coming over.
-Joey?
- 조이
- 알았어, 여기
I know. Here, here.
그게 아니라
No. This is my friend Rachel.
We went to high school together.
내 친구 레이첼이야
고등학교 동창
-Hi.
반갑습니다
안녕하세요
I love you on that show.
그 드라마 정말 좋아해요
I watch you every day.
매일 보거든요
When you took out your own kidney
to save your ex-wife...
자기를 죽이려 했던 전처한테
신장을 기증하는 장면은 정말...
even though
she tried to kill you...
It's always nice to meet fans.
팬을 만나는 건 언제나 즐겁죠
-She's not crazy, is she?
-No.
- 미친 여자 아니지?
- 그럼
So how you doing?
그건 그렇고...
안녕하쇼?
Hang on.
잠깐
Hang on. Hang on.
기다려
대기
Go!
뭐야
누구지?
Who's this?
날 만난 걸 행운으로 알아
You're gonna like working for me.
이름이 뭔데?
What's your name?
What kind of name is "Brindy"?
무슨 이름이 브린디야?
그게, 뭐...
입 다물어
Stop talking.
이제부터 넌 존이야
All right, from now on
your name is Joan.
성은 맘대로 골라
You can pick your own last name.
I can't find my pen.
Did you eat that too?
펜이 안 보여
그것도 먹었냐?
여기 있었구나
-There you are.
-Uh-oh, it's my boss.
주인님 오셨네
그래, 여기 오늘
할 일이 적혀있어
Here's a list of things for you
to do today.
This is gonna be so great.
Thank you so much.
정말 잘된 거야
다시 한 번 고맙다
I gotta go to work. I'm delivering
twins today, but only one of them is mine.
일하러 간다, 오늘 쌍둥이를
받을 건데 그 중 하나는...
내 아이야
"Drop off my dry cleaning.
Pick up my vitamins."
세탁소 들르기
비타민 사오기
"Teach me how to spell vitamins."
비타민 철자 가르쳐주기
"Wear in my new jeans."
새 청바지 길들이기
-You realize what you are, don't you?
-What?
네 역할이 뭔지 알아?
- 뭔데?
- 걔 몸종이야
You're his bitch!
그건 안 돼!
안 돼!
No, no! No!
잠깐, 내 초콜릿
깔고 앉은 거야?
Wait! You didn't sit on my
Kit Kats did you?
No, there was a little,
little dip in the market...
아냐, 오늘 주식시세가
약간 떨어지는 바람에
and I lost 13 million dollars.
1,300만 달러를 날렸어
하지만 초콜릿은 괜찮지?
But the Kit Kats are all right?
난 어떡하면 좋아?
What am I gonna do?
I can't call my office, they'll kill me.
회사에 전화하면 날 죽일 거고
고객한테 전화하면 자살할 텐데
I can't call my clients,
they'll kill themselves!
-Great, now my chest hurts.
-What?
이런, 가슴까지 아프네
뭐?
My chest hurts.
가슴이 아프다고
-And now I can't breathe.
-Are you having a heart attack?
이제 숨도 못 쉬겠다
피비, 너 심장발작이야?
발작이 일어나면 왼쪽 팔에
통증이 오락가락하는 거야?
If I were, would I have shooting
pains up and down my left arm?
맞아
-Yes.
-Then, yes. That is what I'm having.
그럼 나 심장발작이다
어쩜 좋아
Oh, my God!
그래
Okay, this thing is useless.
So will you dial 911 for me?
얘는 이제 쓸모가 없어
911에 전화 좀 해라
Come on, Phoebe, it's not that bad.
피비, 그렇게 상심할 거 없어
Most people would be excited if they
didn't work for a couple weeks.
보통사람들은 몇 주
쉬지 못해 안달을 하는데
Most people don't like their jobs.
I love my job.
그 사람들은 자기 일을
싫어하지만 난 달라
I've been not working for three hours,
and I'm already going crazy.
겨우 세 시간 쉬었는데
벌써 미칠 것 같다니까
I miss Joan.
존이 보고 싶어
심장발작은 좀 쉬는 게
좋다는 자연의 충고야
Honey, having a heart attack is nature's
way of telling you to slow down.
I always thought having a heart attack
was nature's way of telling you to die.
난 심장발작이 죽으라는
자연의 충고인 줄 알았어
You're not gonna die.
넌 안 죽을 거야
I mean, you are going to die,
but you're not gonna die today.
물론 죽긴 하겠지만
오늘은 안 죽어
I wish I was dead.
그냥 날 죽여줘
잠깐 나가자
Let's take a walk.
'함부로 입 놀리기' 잡지에
기고하는 건 어때?
You should consider writing for
Talking Out of Your Ass magazine.
What's going on with you?
넌 요즘 뭐하고 지내?
Well, I've been doing a lot more
of my karate.
그냥...
시간을 더 할애해서
카라테에 열중하고 있지
-Still a dry spell with Carol?
-Yeah.
- 캐롤이랑은 여전히 냉각기고?
- 그래
How long has it been since
you've had sex?
- 잠자리한 지는 얼마나 됐어?
- 글쎄
-Well, last weekend...
-Oh, that's not so bad.
- 지난 주말이...
- 그럼 양호하네
will be two months...
두 달째였지
내가 덤벼들지 않은 게
since I stopped trying.
뭔가 색다른 걸 시도해봐
You need to spice things up.
- 무슨 말이야?
- 글쎄
-What do you mean?
-I don't know.
서로를 밧줄로 묶고
뭔가를 핥아먹는다든가
You could tie her up.
You could eat stuff off each other.
지저분한 얘기나
야시꾸리한 장난감
Dirty talk, menage a trois, toys.
롤플레잉도 있지
Role-playing.
You're the warden, she's the prisoner.
넌 간수, 캐롤은 죄수
넌 해적, 캐롤은 매춘부
-You're the pirate, she's the wench.
-Okay, I think I got it.
무슨 말인지 알겠어
둘 다 주식중개인이 돼서
Or you could be two stockbrokers, and
you're rolling naked on the trading floor...
사람 많은 거래소에서
알몸으로 뒹굴어도 좋고
and everybody's watching.
It never happened.
그런 적 없었어
Sorry.
괜찮지?
-So how is it going with Joey?
-Just great. He beeps me now with codes.
조이랑은 어때?
좋지, 이제는
신호음으로 호출해
One is: "Bring me food."
한 번은 '먹을 거 가져와'
Two is:
"I'm with a girl. Bring us food."
두 번은 '여자랑 있다
먹을 거 더 가져와'
Three is:
"I'm lost and I can't find food."
세 번은 '먹을 거
다 어디 간 거야?'
Oh, sweetie.
힘내
Is there any food around here?
여기 먹을 거 안 팔아?
-Is she gonna be all right?
-Yeah, she's in there.
피비는 괜찮아?
- 응, 안에 있어
- 그래
Oh, great.
이런, 바지 그만 벗어라
제대로 된 것 같다
Go take off those pants.
They look ready.
실버컵 스튜디오
And over there is Brady's Pub...
저긴 가끔 한 잔하고 싶을 때
찾는 브래디의 술집입니다
where I like to unwind
after a long day of "surgeoning."
너무 근사해요
또 뭐가 있죠?
This is so amazing. What else?
Well, that is a large piece
of television equipment.
저건 커다란 촬영장비
And that is an old man.
이쪽은 영감님
어이, 영감님
-Hey, old man!
-Hey.
안녕하세요
Alrighty. What do you say we head
back to my place?
그럼 이제 저희 집으로 가시죠
You know, I would really love to,
but I shouldn't.
물론 가고는 싶지만
관두는 게 좋겠어요
왜죠? 뭣 때문에 세상을
멈출 수 없는 겁니까
Why?
Why can't the world stop turning...
잠시 우리 둘만을 위해
just for a moment, just for us?
Isn't that a line from the show?
드라마에 나온 대사죠?
네, 하지만...
Yeah, but...
그런 대사를 읊긴 읊었어도
진심으로 말한 적은 없습니다
I may have said
those things before, but...
I never truly meant them until now.
지금까지는
That's a line from the show too!
그것도 드라마에 나왔어요
Okay, you watch too much TV.
TV 너무 많이 보시네요
Here's the freshly
squeezed orange juice you asked for.
조이, 여기 방금 짠
오렌지주스 가져왔다
Thanks.
고마워
건더기가 있잖아
There's pulp in that.
그래서?
I thought we talked about this.
I don't like pulp.
얘기했잖아
난 건더기 싫어
No pulp. Pulp isn't juice.
All juice.
건더기는 주스가 아냐
주스만 달라고, 알았어?
미안하다, 내가
건더기를 좋아해서
I'm sorry.
I guess I just like the pulp.
I am being so rude.
내가 너무 무례했구나
그냥 소다수나 드실래요?
Rachel, would you like a soda
or something?
Because Chandler will
run right out and get it.
챈들러가 번개처럼
대령할 겁니다
네, 그럼 아이스티 주세요
Yeah, well, sure,
iced tea would be great.
그러죠, 아이스티래
Iced tea.
좋습니다
Okay. Anything for you, sir?
주인님은 뭘 드시렵니까?
제가 말하지 않았던가요?
Did I not just tell him?
챈들러, 내가 말을 하면
귀를 쫑긋 세우고 들어야지
Okay, look, Chandler,
if this is gonna work...
you have got to listen.
You're gonna throw that juice at me,
aren't you?
그 주스 끼얹을 거야?
It's not all juice.
주스 아니라면서
오늘 아침에 좋았지?
So, honey, this morning was fun, huh?
자기 샤워하는데
내가 뛰어 들어가서...
Me hopping in on you
in the shower there?
그래, 조만간 욕실이
두 개 딸린 집을 얻자
Yeah, maybe someday we could get
a place with two bathrooms.
Look, Carol, I was thinking maybe...
저기, 캐롤...
우리 조금 색다른 걸
시도해보는 게 어떨까?
Maybe we can spice things
up a little.
무슨 말이야?
-What do you mean?
-Carol, our sex life. It's just not..
우리 성생활에 문제가...
아빠!
-Dad!
-Hey there, little fella!
그래, 내 아들
Why don't we
get some shoes on you, huh?
우리 신발 신어볼까?
Why don't you show Dad how you
can put your shoes on in your room.
방에서 신발 어떻게 신는지
아빠한테 보여줄래?
네
그렇지!
우리 성생활 말이야
Seriously, our sex life.
생각해봤는데...
I was thinking maybe, I don't know...
참신한 시도 어때?
그냥 재미 삼아
we could try some new
things, you know, for fun.
-Like what?
-Well, I don't know.
- 어떤 거?
- 나도 모르겠지만...
What if we were to...
두 사람이 서로...
tie each other up?
서로 묶는다든가
Some people eat stuff
off one another.
어떤 사람들은
뭘 핥아먹기도 한대
그래
Yeah.
You know, we could try dirty talk.
지저분한 얘기를
할 수도 있고
-We could have a threesome.
-I love that idea!
세 명이서 해본다거나
그거 괜찮겠다
Who sold a story to Archie Comics?
'아치 코믹스'에
스토리를 팔았어
세상에, 너무 잘됐다
Oh, my God, that's so great.
이제 출판 작가네
선물이라도 줘야하는데
You're a published writer.
I wish I had a present for you.
Wait a minute.
잠깐
마지막 남은 초콜릿
My last Kit Kat bar.
- 나눠먹을까?
- 그래
-You want to share it?
-Okay!
- 있었구나
- 그래
화난 거 알고 있어
정말 미안하다
Chandler, I know you're mad.
I'm sorry.
I was a total jerk.
Completely over the line.
내가 나쁜 놈이야
완전히 선을 넘어버렸어
I just... I hate pulp.
건더기가 싫은 걸 어떡해?
You know how Monica feels
about low-fat mayonnaise?
모니카가 저지방 마요네즈
싫어하는 것처럼
그건 마요네즈도 아냐
It's not mayonnaise!
Anyway, I just wanted to say
I'm sorry, and here.
어쨌든 내 사과를
받아줬으면 좋겠어
그리고 이거
뭔데?
-What's this?
-Fresh-squeezed orange juice, with pulp.
방금 짠 오렌지주스
건더기도 포함해서
-Just the way you like it.
-Thanks, man.
네 취향대로
고맙다
Hey, Joey.
조이
Joey? Chandler sold a story
to Archie Comics.
조이?
챈들러가 '아치 코믹스'에
스토리를 팔았대
정말 잘됐네, 축하한다
That's great! Congratulations!
What's the story?
어떤 스토리인데?
You wouldn't care.
It's just a stupid comic book story.
넌 몰라도 돼
그냥 만화책인데 뭐
무슨 소리야, 나 아치랑
그 일당 엄청 좋아해
Are you kidding me?
I love Archie and the whole gang.
Well, Archie needs money
to fix his jalopy.
그게...
아치가 고물차를 수리할
돈이 필요해졌거든
But he doesn't want Reggie
to just give him the money.
하지만 레지한테서
공돈을 받긴 싫었어
So Reggie hires him as his assist..
그래서 레지가 아치를 조수로...
As his butler.
집사로 고용한 다음
And then makes him do crazy things...
덩어리 없는 밀크셰이크를
만들라는 둥 억지를 막 부려
Like bring him milk shakes
that can't have lumps in them.
Wait a minute.
That sounds a little familiar.
잠깐, 어디서 들어본 얘긴데
Did they already do that one?
I think I read it!
나왔던 얘기 아냐?
읽어본 거 같아
모니카, 물어볼 게 있어
Monica, listen. I have to ask.
조이 트리비아니가
날 자기 집에 초대했는데
Okay, Joey Tribbiani invited me back
to his apartment.
-Does he do this with a lot of girls?
-Yeah, a lot. A lot, a lot.
그런 여자가 많았니?
그래, 많았지
셀 수도 없이
내가 그 중 하나가 되다니
And I'm one of them.
도저히 믿을 수 없어
조이 트리비아니가
I just cannot believe this.
I mean, Joey Tribbiani.
성까지 부를 건 없어
You don't have to use his last name.
But, Monica, come on,
it's Joey Tribbiani.
모니카, 무슨 소리야
조니 트리비아니인데
I guess you have to.
그럼 부르든지
상관할 바는 아니지만
너 결혼하지 않았니?
It's none of my business,
but aren't you married?
맞아
Yeah.
I wish we could just not be married
for a little bit.
아주 잠깐만이라도
미혼이었음 좋겠다
그니까 잠시 헤어진 상태라든가
You know, I just wish we could be,
like, on a break.
그것도 아니네요
Well, you're not.
It's easy for you. You're not married.
You can have sex with whoever you want.
너야 홀몸이니 누구랑 자든
부담 없고 얼마나 좋아
물론이지
Yeah, I can.
내가 안 할 줄 아니?
틈만 나면 한다니까
Don't think I don't. I do.
I mean, all the time. You bet!
- 모니카?
- 응?
Monica?
You've done it, right?
너도 해봤다 이거지?
당연하지
Of course I have. What do you think,
I'm, like, some 30-year-old virgin?
내가 서른 먹고도
처녀라고 생각해?
세상에, 너 서른
먹고도 처녀구나
Oh, my God.
You're a 30-year-old virgin.
Say it louder. The guy
in the back didn't hear you.
더 크게 말해라
저 남자도 듣게
네, 들었어요
Yeah, I heard it.
물론 기회는 몇 번 있었지만
완벽한 남자를 기다리는 중이야
It's not like I haven't had the
opportunity.
I'm just waiting for the perfect guy.
로저란 남자를 사귀고 있는데
완벽하지는 않지만
I'm seeing this guy Roger.
He's not perfect...
but I'm thinking maybe I should
get it over with.
해치워버려야겠어
내 꽃을 줄 거야
You know, give him my flower.
그래, 줘버려
Oh, my God, do it!
Honey, you've waited long enough.
너무 오래 기다렸어
-You know what? You are right.
-Sex doesn't have to be a big deal.
그렇지, 네 말이 맞아
그럼, 섹스가 뭐 별거야?
규칙이나 금기는
다 없어져야 돼
There shouldn't be all these
rules and restrictions.
People should be able to sleep
with whoever they want, whenever..
마음에 들면 누가 됐든
언제가 됐든...
Rachel, I'm never gonna think it's
okay for you to cheat on your husband.
레이첼, 그렇다고 남편 몰래
바람피우는 건 곤란하지
숫처녀 주제에 뭘 안다고!
What do you know, virgin?
피비
Phoebe?
Why is smoke coming out
of the bathroom?
왜 화장실에서 연기가 나와?
The doctor said that could be
one of the side effects.
의사 말이 이것도 부작용이래
피비, 당장 담배 꺼
Put the cigarette out.
담배가 아니라 내 몸에서
나는 연기라니까
No, it's not a cigarette.
The smoke is coming out of me!
어서 꺼
-Put it out.
-Okay, okay!
알았어, 끄면 되잖아
와줘서 고맙다
-I'm so glad you're here.
-Come on.
이리 누워
-I got it.
-Give it to me!
- 내가 받을게
- 어서 내놔
- 내가 받아
- 이리 줘
-I got it.
-Give it!
여보세요?
Hello?
She can't come to the phone now.
지금은 전화 못 받는데요
네, 그러죠
알겠습니다
Right. No problem.
Okay, bye-bye.
네, 그럼
회사야? 화났어?
잭이야? 소리치던?
Was it my work? Were they mad?
Was it Jack? Did he yell?
진정해, 소리친 사람 없어
No, just relax. Nobody yelled.
잭이 너 괜찮은지
알아보려고 전화한 거야
Jack was making sure you
were getting better.
다행이네
Thank God.
쟤 짤렸다
Yeah, she's fired.
You've done all you can, Dr. Wesley.
박사님은 최선을 다하셨어요
편안히 보내드리세요
You've got to let her go.
Goodbye and Godspeed, Hope Brady.
그럼 잘 가요, 호프 브래디
어림없다, 웨슬리
Not so fast, Wesley.
Ramoray!
라모레, 이 놈...
그렇다, 웨슬리
That's right, Wesley.
이 말을 하러 왔다
I just stopped by to say that
you're not a real doctor.
돌팔이 의사 놈아
저 환자의 뇌는
지극히 정상이야
And that woman's brain is fine.
어머, 다행이다
Oh, thank God.
호프
-Hope? Hope?
-Drake.
호프
드레이크
You're not dying, Hope.
당신은 죽지 않아요
오래오래 행복하게 살 거예요
You're gonna live a long,
healthy life. With me.
나와 함께
Oh, Drake.
드레이크
좋아
Okay.
그래
Here we go.
좋았어
안녕하세요, 조이
레이첼이에요
Hi, Joey? It's Rachel.
I am free tomorrow night.
저 내일 밤에 한가한데
네, 그럼요
샌드위치 사가죠 뭐
Yeah, sure, sure,
I can bring some sandwiches.
So, honey...
저기, 자기야...
세 명이 같이 하는 거 말인데
this threesome thing?
How are we even gonna start to find..?
상대를 어떻게 찾을지...
실은 내가 아는 여자들 중에서
후보를 다 목록으로 뽑아봤어
Actually, I'm making a list of women
I know who might be into this.
Boy.
저런
숙제 열심히 했네?
Someone's been
doing their homework.
게일 로스튼은 두 번 썼는데
걔가 워낙...
I know Gail Rosten
is in there twice...
but she is so....
나도 알아
Oh, I know.
얘기만 하고 있어도 좀...
You know, just talking about it
is getting me kind of...
I know. Me too.
나도 그래
정말? 벤은 잘 거야
I think Ben's asleep.
있지...
You know, I think it'll be
better if we just save it.
아껴두는 게 좋겠어
맞아
그렇지, 아껴두자
참을 수 있어
Right. Save it.
I can do that.
베스 이스라엘 의료센터
Why do you always wear
that dumb hat?
그 바보 같은 모자 좀 벗어라
왜, 신문배달이 늦었어?
What, you late for your paper route?
"Hi, Mr. and Mrs. Jones.
Here's your paper.
'존스 씨, 신문 왔습니다
유리창 깨서 죄송해요'
I'm sorry about your window."
Hey, Phoebe.
- 안녕, 피비?
- 어서 와
좀 어때?
How's it going?
여기서 나가고 싶어
내가 미친다고, 미쳐!
I've got to get out of this bed.
I'm going crazy here! Crazy!
Here you go, sweetie.
자, 마셔
뭔데? 허브티?
난 허브티 싫어
What the hell is this, herbal tea?
I hate herbal tea.
Well, I put some honey in it.
- 꿀도 좀 넣었는데
- 냥냥냥냥...
아직 해고당한 줄 모르지?
-She doesn't know she was fired?
-No, the doctors say it may kill her.
의사가 그 얘기 들으면
죽을지도 모른대
거기 두 계집애는
뭘 쑥덕거리냐?
What are you girls
whispering about over there?
아무래도 얘기해야겠다
But I think we should tell her.
Look, Phoebe, maybe this whole
heart-attack thing is a sign...
이번 심장발작은
어떤 계시 아닐까?
that you should start thinking
about getting a different job.
다른 직업을 찾아보라는
이건 뭐 바보 콘테스트야?
거기 너 1등 먹어라
Okay, what is this,
a stupid contest?
Because we've got a winner here.
로스 말이 맞아
31살에 심장발작이라니
He's right. People are not supposed
to have heart attacks at 31.
그건 알지만 지금 내가
무슨 일을 하겠어?
I know. But if I didn't work there,
what else would I do?
너 기타 연주했잖아
-You used to like playing the guitar.
-That was lucrative. Smart like your brother.
그거 돈 많이 벌겠다
오빠처럼 똑똑하시네
What about the massage thing?
That never gave you a heart attack.
안마사로 일하면
심장마비는 안 걸릴 텐데
Pulling in a salary
in the high six figures...
몇 십만 달러씩 벌다가
푼돈 받고 알몸을 문질러라
or rubbing gross naked people
for chump change.
뭘 하는 게 좋을까?
What do I do? What will I do?
참 사실적이네요
I mean, it's just so realistic.
그렇죠?
I know.
His name's Pat.
이름은 '토닥이'예요
Pat the dog.
'토닥이'는 개라
오! 오! 그렇구나!
I get it!
세상에...
저기...
Ready for a refill?
더 드릴까요?
지금도 알딸딸해요
I probably shouldn't.
그니까 더 마실래요
So I will!
-It's like it's raining.
-Pretty cool, huh?
꼭 비 오는 거 같네요
멋지죠?
But if you think you could put a fish
in there...
그렇다고 저기다 물고기를
넣으면 바로 작살난답니다
and it wouldn't get sucked into
the mechanism, you'd be wrong.
Can I use your bathroom?
화장실 좀 쓸까요?
It's right through there.
저쪽으로 돌아가세요
이거 알아요?
You know, I gotta tell you.
일주일 전만 해도
상상이나 했겠어요?
If someone told me a week ago...
that I would be peeing
in Joey Tribbiani's apartment...
내가 조이 트리비아니의
아파트에서 쉬를 하다니
그래서 인생은 뒤웅박이죠
Life's pretty great, isn't it?
시장하죠?
I hope you're hungry.
굴부터 먹어요
We're starting with oysters.
You know what they say about oysters,
don't you?
굴이 어떤 음식인지 알죠?
They have parasites?
기생충 있다고요?
아뇨
어떤 사람들은 굴을
최음제라고 한대요
Some people say that oysters
are an aphrodisiac.
- 어떤 사람들이?
- 사람들
-What people?
-People.
People say it.
사람들 얘기예요
이리 와요
Come here.
굴이라고요?
So, oysters, huh?
다음에는 중동산
쿠스쿠스를 먹어요
Then we'll have a little
Middle Eastern couscous.
이건 손으로
집어먹어야 제 맛이죠
Something we can eat...
with our hands.
재미는 있겠지만
전염병의 우려가...
When we were studying
communicable diseases..
그런 거 하지 말고...
No, no. No.
It's sensual.
관능적이잖아요
- 몰랐네, 좋아요
- 그럼요
Didn't know. Okay.
안 돼
미안해요, 병원이군요
Sorry, it's the hospital.
The food looks great.
Save me some?
먹음직스러운데
좀 남겨둘래요?
그건 보장 못해요
I can't promise anything.
진짜로 하게 됐구나
We're really gonna do this?
그런 거 같아
Looks like it.
알겠지만...
If this is too weird for you,
you can still back out anytime..
자기한테 너무 부담되면
언제라도 그만 둘 수...
- 내가 나갈게
- 그래
I got it!
- 수잔, 어서 와
- 안녕
-Thank you so much for coming.
-I wouldn't have missed it for the world.
와줘서 정말 고마워
누구 부탁인데 거절해
전 로스라고 합니다
I'm Ross, by the way.
안녕, 로스
Hello, Ross.
집을 정말 예쁘게 꾸며놨구나
-I love what you've done with this space.
-Thank you so much.
고마워
이거 아찔한데?
How hot is this?!
로저가 아니라
내가 있어서 어떡하니
I'm sorry you're here with me instead
of Roger.
그러게
Yeah, me too.
내가 로저처럼 해보지 뭐
Well, I could make it seem like
he's here.
"Here's some little-known facts
about couscous:
쿠스쿠스에는 숨겨진
진실이 있어요
1979년까지는 그냥 '쿠스'였죠
They didn't add the second 'cous'
until 1979."
그만해, 하나도 안 웃겨
Stop it! That's not funny!
알았어
미안해, 그냥...
I'm sorry, okay?
It's just...
오늘밤엔 나름대로...
tonight was supposed to be
a big deal.
계획이 있었거든
- 뭔데 그래?
- 넌 알 필요 없어
-What was tonight?
-You don't want to know.
알았다
글쎄 뭐냐고?
What was tonight?
오늘밤...
Tonight was going to be
my first time.
첫경험을 하고 싶었어
로저랑?
With Roger?
인생을 통틀어서?
Not just with Roger?
엄마야
Oh, my God.
All right, relax,
Mr. I've-Had-Sex-Four-Times!
그래, 너 섹스 네 번
한 거 큰 벼슬이다
Four different women!
여자가 네 명이었다고
I've had sex way more times.
섹스 횟수는 훨씬 더 많아
-How many?
-Nine.
얼마나?
아홉 번
I'm just waiting for the perfect guy.
완벽한 남자를 기다렸던 거야
Good for you. You really think
that Roger's the perfect guy?
그래, 잘했다
그럼 로저가 완벽하냐?
그냥 나쁜 사람은 아니니까
No, but he's not a horrible guy.
That's what I tell girls about me.
여자들이 날 그렇게 아는데
나 처녀귀신으로 늙어죽겠다
Chandler, I'm gonna die a virgin!
그렇지 않아, 넌 괜찮은
애니까 분명 잘될 거야
No, you are not.
You are sweet and wonderful...
and this is gonna happen for you.
Oh, really? When?
Do you want to do it with me?
정말? 언제?
- 너라면 나랑 하겠어?
- 그럼
Okay.
I was kidding.
농담이었어
마찬가지야
So was I.
조이
당신은 정말 훌륭한 배우예요
You're such an amazing actor.
언제 닥터 드레이크
라모레의 탈을 벗고
How do you know where
Dr. Drake Ramoray leaves off...
조이 트리비아니가 되죠?
and Joey Tribbiani begins?
드레이크 박사의 경우엔
Well, with Dr. Drake...
남이 시키는 대로 말하지만
they always tell me what to say.
조이의 경우엔
스스로 말을 지어내죠
And with Joey, I pretty much have to
make it up on my own.
Tell me something, Joey.
궁금한 게 있는데...
- 소파에서 떨어졌네요
- 그렇군요
-I just fell right off the couch there.
-Yeah, you did.
- 괜찮아요
- 이쪽으로 앉아요
Here you go.
Let me ask you a question.
- 하나 좀 물어볼까요?
- 네
당신이 정말 아름답다는 말을
들어본 지 얼마나 됐죠?
When was the last time...
someone told you
just how beautiful you are?
Wow.
손에 감각이 없네요
I can't feel my hands.
어디 볼까요?
Come on. Come here.
- 안 될 말이지
- 그럼
We can't do this.
- 굴 먹을래?
- 응
Oyster?
만약 하게 된다면
난 너무 부담스러워
If we did do this,
there'd be a lot of pressure on me.
너무 오랫동안 기다린 널
실망시키면 안 되잖아
Because you've waited a long time,
and I wouldn't want to disappoint you.
하지만 난 비교할
대상이 없는걸?
But I have nothing to compare it to.
네가 형편없더라도
내가 어떻게 아나?
Even if you were horrible,
how would I know?
그건 좋구나
I do like that.
내가 더 힘들어
경쟁상대가 넷이잖아
It's harder for me.
I have four women to compete with.
사실대로 말하면 셋이야
Well, if it helps,
there were only three.
딱 오늘밤만이다, 좋지?
So it'd just be for tonight, right?
그럼, 친구가 친구를
돕는 거라고 생각해
Absolutely. It would just be one
friend helping out another friend.
그만해, 이럼 안 돼
Stop it. We're not doing this.
하자
-Let's do it!
-No!
- 안 돼, 좋아
- 그래
Okay!
그럼...
어떻게 시작하는지 알아?
Do you have any moves?
조금 알지
I have some moves.
- 난 몰라
- 좋아
I have no moves.
뭐하는 거야?
Okay, what you doing there?
미안해, 너무 이상해서
-I'm sorry, this is just too weird.
-Yeah, forget it.
그래, 관두자
- 불을 끄면 어떨까?
- 좋지
What if I turn out the lights?
그렇지
- 챈들러?
- 응?
그건 소파야
That's the couch.
I know.
나도 알아
Oh, my God!
엄마야
I know!
그러게
I'll tell you something.
저기 있잖아
We are gonna do that again!
우리 한 번 더 하자
좋지
잘 잤어요?
Morning.
- 네
- 그래요
Oh, right.
Oh, God.
맙소사
Oh, I can't believe Joey Tribbiani
heard me throw up.
조이 트리비아니한테
토하는 소리를 들려주다니
He actually saw you a little bit too.
실은 조금 보기도 했어요
안 돼
세상에, 우리 혹시...
Oh, God, we didn't...?
아뇨, 아니에요
그 꼴을 보고 어떻게
Not after seeing that.
God, I'm just a horrible person.
난 정말 나쁜 여자예요
왜요?
-Wh..? Why?
-Because I'm married.
나 결혼했어요
네, 유부녀예요
That's right, I'm a married woman.
I came to a TV star's apartment
to have an affair.
근데 바람이나 피우려고
인기스타의 집에 오다니
말도 안 돼요
That's ridiculous.
I'm not a "star."
난 스타가 아니에요
그냥 평범한 유명배우죠
I'm just a regular famous actor.
And I'm a horrible, horrible person.
네, 그리고 난 정말
끔찍한 계집애죠
그렇게 얘기하지 말아요
Rachel, will you stop saying that?
이거 봐요
Hey, look.
기억나요? 드라마에서
카프리가 죽으면서 나한테...
Remember on the show
when Capri was dying?
-And she gave me..
-The ring from the cave.
동굴에서 주운 반지를 줬죠
하여간...
어머나, 소품을 가져와도 돼요?
Oh, my God!
They let you keep that stuff?
그럼요
Sure. As long as they don't find out,
you can keep whatever you want.
들키지만 않으면 뭐든 괜찮아요
받아주세요
And I want you to have it.
- 안 돼요
- 괜찮아요
No, I couldn't.
이걸 볼 때마다
Every time you look at it...
자신이 좋은 사람이라는
사실을 꼭 기억해요
I want you to remember
that you are a good person.
Now, you had the chance to cheat...
바람피울 기회가 있었지만
게다가 상대는 난데
and with me.
그러지 않았어요
이 반지는 그걸 뜻해요
But you didn't.
And that's what this ring stands for.
하지만 그건 친오빠를 향한
사랑을 뜻하는 거 아니에요?
But I thought that ring stood for
Capri's undying love for her brother.
- 가질래요, 말래요?
- 줘요
Look, you want the ring or not?
저런, 일어났구나
Hey, look at you! You're up!
다행이다
I thought I'd try to take a walk.
좀 걷고 싶어서
물 좀 떠놓을래?
금방 올게
Will you pour me some water?
I'll be back soon.
공중전화로 회사에
연락할 거 아니지?
You're not gonna use
the pay phone to call work, are you?
아냐, 나도 배운 게 있어
No. I've learned my lesson.
좋아, 빨리 떠야지
Let's go! Come on!
Move it!
가자니까
Phoebe, come on!
구두, 가방... 고마워요
쓸개 빨리 치료하세요
Shoes, briefcase. Thanks, Lou.
Good luck with the gallbladder.
조이, 너...
Hey, Joe...
셋이서 해본 적 있냐?
did you ever have a threesome?
글쎄
물론 캐롤도 괜찮고
너도 매력적이지만...
Look, Ross, I think Carol's great,
and I'm sure you're very attractive, but...
내가 미쳐
그런 뜻이 아니라...
No. The reason I'm asking is that...
I sort of had one last night.
어젯밤에 그걸 해봤거든
You?
- 네가?
- 응
그래서?
All right. So? Was it amazing?
좋았어?
그냥...
It was...
괜찮았어
okay.
그냥 괜찮아?
제대로 한 거 맞아?
Just okay? Did you do it right?
Look, it's just, did you ever
go to a party and think:
너 파티 같은 데서
이런 생각해봤냐?
'내가 여기서 사라져도
신경 쓸 사람 있을까?'
"Would anyone really miss me
if I weren't here?"
그래도, 로스
But still, Ross...
두 여자랑 하다 망쳤다?
아무렴 다른 때보다 못했을까
your worst day with two women,
pretty much better than any other day.
그러게 말이야
- 참 내
- 그거 참
근데...
It's just...
내 역할은 일찍 끝나버리고
my part seemed to be over
pretty quickly...
기다리는 시간이 꽤 길었거든
and then there was
a lot of waiting around.
하지만 상대가 둘이잖아
But you got to be with both of them.
Not really.
정확히는 아니었어
Just Carol.
캐롤이랑만 했거든
-Not the other one?
-No, she kept kicking me away.
- 다른 한 명은?
- 그 여잔 날 차내기만 했어
- 시킨 것도 아닌데?
- 그럼
You don't want that.
At least you got to
see a lot of stuff.
그래도 눈요기는 실컷 했겠다
맞아, 아주 장관이더라
Oh, I saw a lot of stuff.
- 심심했어?
- 약간
-You get a little bored?
-A little.
Made a snack.
새참도 만들어 먹었다
- 뭘 먹었는데?
- 그냥 샌드위치
-What'd you have?
-Just a sandwich.
Turkey. A little mustard.
칠면조에다 겨자 좀 넣고
- 맛있었겠다
- 그럼, 죽였지
-Sounds good.
-It really was.
- 나야
- 그래
내가 어제 누구랑 잤는지 알아?
Let me tell you about this chick
I scored with last night.
이런, 잠깐
너였구나
Wait a minute, that was you.
이거 어때?
Hey, check me out. I'm a slut!
나 걸레다
저기, 오늘밤엔 어때?
So you want to do something tonight?
안 돼, 로저가 올 거야
I can't.
Dr. Roger's coming over again.
Oh, right.
그렇구나
아직 사귀는 사이지?
Because you're still seeing him,
and he's a good guy.
좋은 사람이야
전에 한번은...
I remember a time....
Are you okay?
- 너 괜찮아?
- 그럼, 물론이지
Yeah, totally.
Totally. Are you?
괜찮아, 넌?
Great. It's so amazing.
좋아, 잘된 거야
지난번에 로저가 왔을 땐
너무 긴장했었는데
Last time Dr. Roger came over,
I was so nervous.
너랑 그러고 나니까
'박사, 너 빨랑 나와'
But after being with you,
I'm like, "Can the doctor see me now?"
곧 오겠지
I bet he can.
"l don't have an appointment,
but I sure could use a physical."
약속한 건 없지만
몸으로 부딪히면 돼
너 정말 괜찮아?
-You sure you're okay?
-Don't worry about me, I'll be fine.
그럼, 걱정 마
난 멀쩡해
맙소사, 배리
My God! Barry!
주말엔 안 들어온다면서
You said you were going to
be away all weekend!
그랬지, 미안해
내가 좀 일렀지?
That's right! I'm sorry!
I am early!
그럼 마저 끝내
Finish, please!
놀랐지? 누가 왔나봐
Surprise! Look who's back!
- 이런, 피비
- 안녕
경비원 불러
Call security.
피비, 해고당하지 않았나?
Phoebe, didn't you get fired?
그럴 리가
I don't think so.
피비?
잭, 안녕하세요
-What are you doing here?
-All better. Back to work.
- 여긴 웬일이야?
- 나아서 일하러 왔죠
시장조사부의 머저리가
나더러 해고됐다는데
This clown from research
told me I was fired.
조사가 부실했군요
He should do his research, huh?
해고된 거 맞아
Well, you were fired.
아냐, 잉
I told that guy
who answered your phone.
전화 받은 친구한테 얘기했어
난 들은 말 없으니까
그건 무효예요
I didn't get that message.
So this doesn't count.
내 방으로 갈게요
Anyway, I'll be in my office.
Phoebe, you don't have an office.
피비, 자네 방은 없어
괜찮아요, 여기서 일하죠 뭐
I'll work right here.
좋네요, 싱싱한 풀도 있고
This is good. Next to this plant.
- 이거 봐, 그러지 말고...
- 여긴 내 방이에요
You're in my office.
보세요, 난 이 회사에
큰돈을 벌어줬어요
I've made a lot of cash for this
company. I am talking big bucks!
한두 푼이 아니라고요
페소, 엔, 루블
작은 실수 한 번에...
Pesos! Yen! Rubles!
You make one little mistake..
1,300만 달러야
You lost 13 million dollars.
그니까 돈이 문제였군요
So now this is all about money?
아무리 그렇다고...
You know, it's bad enough that...
You have got to be kidding.
농담이 심하시네요
괜찮아?
-Are you all right?
-I'm having another heart attack.
- 또 심장발작이에요
- 뭐?
또 심장발작이라고요
I'm having another heart attack!
911에 전화해
Call 911!
Dumb-ass!
푼수때기야
안녕, 피비
어떻게 지내요?
Phoebe, how's it going?
They fired me, and I'm having
a heart attack.
밥줄 떨어지고
심장마비까지 왔어
- 돌아와서 반가워요
- 그래
Well, welcome back.
- 안녕, 로스
- 어서 와, 레이첼
Is Joey Tribbiani here?
조이 트리비아니 있어?
아니
그 사람 보면 내가 애타게
찾는다고 전해 줘
If you see him, please tell him
I'm looking for him...
이번엔 절대 토하지 않겠다고
and that this time
I am not gonna throw up!
Well, that's always good news.
그렇다면 다행이지
Are you okay?
무슨 일 있어?
나? 난 괜찮아
Me? I'm great!
미치고 팔짝 뛰게 좋아
I'm fine! I'm so good!
하지만 안 좋은 게 있어
But you know who's not great?
사내놈들
Men!
- 너도 남자지?
- 그래
You're a man, right, Ross?
- 앉아
- 응
Sit down.
하나만 물어보자
Let me ask you something.
Do wedding vows mean squat
to you people?
혼인서약이라는 게
너희들한텐 개똥이야?
어째서 내가 집을
비우겠다고 한 순간
Why is it that the second
we tell you we are going out of town...
bam, there you are in bed
with the neighbor's dog-walker?
이웃집 개 산책시키는 애랑
침대로 기어들어 가는 거냐고
We're sorry.
우리가 잘못했다
아니, 진심으로 묻는 거야
No, seriously. Seriously. What has
happened to the sanctity of marriage?
결혼의 신성함은
대체 어디로 갔냐고?
너 어젯밤에
조이 집에 안 갔냐?
-Didn't you spend last night at Joey's?
-What are you, a detective?
너 무슨 탐정이니?
너희 부부 일은 내가 잘 모르고
I don't know what's going on
with you and your husband...
개 산책시키는 애가
성인이길 바라지만
and what is hopefully
an adult dog-walker.
모든 남자가 다 그런 건 아냐
Look, can I just say,
not all men are like that.
가정을 지키기 위해 기꺼이
희생을 감수하는 남자도 있어
There are men who'll do anything
to make their marriage work.
누군 옆에서 구경만 했다더라
Men who will stand by and watch...
마누라가 자기만 쏙 빼놓고
다른 여자랑 뒹굴었는데도
as their wives engage in what can
only be described as a "twosome"...
상대는 헬스클럽에서
인사나 나누던 사이였지
with some woman she barely knows
from the gym!
그 남자가 누구야?
Who are these men?
Just men. A guy I know.
그 남자? 그냥 아는 사람
그 사람한테 전해라
마누라가 레즈비언이라고
Well, you might want to tell him
it sounds like his wife...
is gay.
She is not...
그렇지 않아...
She's gay.
레즈비언이네
맙소사
Oh, my God.
골수 레즈비언이야
She is so gay!
이럴 순 없어
I can't believe this.
Good day for married people, huh?
기혼자 수난의 날이로군
I'm sorry your husband cheated on you.
남편이 바람을
피웠다니 유감이다
I'm sorry your wife is gay.
마누라가 레즈비언이라니
유감이다
I guess women aren't that great either.
여자도 별수 없는 모양이구나
Try telling my wife that.
내 마누라한테 그 얘기해 줘
Okay to come in?
들어가도 돼?
Come in, eat, whatever you want.
그래, 들어와서 아무거나 먹어
Dr. Roger got beeped again.
로저는 또 호출 받고 갔어
알아, 누가 호출했게?
Yeah, I know. Guess who beeped him.
- 뭐?
- 내가 바로 탈장 환자야
I'm the ruptured spleen.
Why would you do that?
왜 그랬어?
넌 그 사람이랑 있으면 안 돼
Because you shouldn't be with him.
You should be with me.
나랑 있어야지
Really?
정말?
네가 로저 얘기를 할 때면
난 너무 고통스러워
When you were talking about Roger,
that was killing me.
어젯밤 같은 일은
그냥 생기는 게 아냐
Things like last night,
they don't just happen.
최소한 내 경우엔
At least not to me. I mean,
with the other two women...
예전 두 여자를 봐도
in the morning, I couldn't wait
to go hang out with my friends.
아침에 일어나면 친구 놈들
만나고 싶어 몸살이 났는데
But with you...
너와 함께라면...
I was, you know,
already with a friend.
벌써 친구가 옆에 있는 거잖아
챈들러
You probably don't want
to go out with me.
넌 내가 싫을지도 모르지
늘 헛소리만 지껄이고
I make too many jokes, I've never
been in a serious relationship...
연애도 못해본 인간이고
더군다나 '닥터'도 아니고
and I'm not technically a "doctor."
사실은 한 명뿐이었지?
There was just one woman,
wasn't there?
둘이었다니까
No, there were two.
- 나까지 합쳐서?
- 그럼
-Including me?
-Oh, yeah.
심장발작 두 번에
결국 깨닫게 됐지
It only takes two heart attacks
To finally make you see
첫 번째는 아니지만
두 번째는 자유라네
One of them won't do it
But the second will set you free
모든 증오와 분노에
작별을 고해요
Tell all your hate and anger
It's time to say goodbye
나도 그렇게 하려네
그 망할 놈들 다 뒈지고 나면
And that is just what I will do
Soon as those bastards I worked for
Die